Hi YiWen,
 
Congratulations on the paper acceptance!
 
Thank you for sending the plan; it looks good to me.  There was quite
a lot of discussion about the paper, mostly focusing on issues #01 and
#06, so I would say those are the most important to focus on.
 
As you say for the plan in #06, massaging the focus towards a the
popularity metric and how to use it is probably the most important
item to address the issues most important to the reviewers.  Issue #01
is related, because it seems to be the missing link: we need to
understand whether it's luck that Repy only uses popular paths, or how
good of an approximation to locking only to popular paths Repy gives
you, or how Repy is an instance of a more general approach towards
locking to popular paths.  I agree that your plan to add
clarifications and discussion in 4.2 and 4.3 seems like the right
place to address it.
 
If you have any questions, let me know, and I look forward to reading
the next version!
 
Thanks,
Dan